{
    "1": {
        "question": "Which of these countries does NOT border the Czech Republic?",
        "answers": {"1": "Germany", "2": "Poland", "3": "Slovaka", "4": "Hungary", "5": "Austria"},
        "correct": "4",
        "answerimage": "Geography-czechrepublic.gif"},
    "2": {
        "question": "What is the capital of South Africa?",
        "answers": {"1": "Johannesburg", "2": "Cape Town", "3": "Pretoria", "4": "Durban", "5": "Nairobi"},
        "correct": "3",
        "explanation": ""},
    "3": {
        "question": "Which city is NOT in India?",
        "answers": {"1": "Ahmedabad", "2": "Madurai", "3": "Mandalay", "4": "Nashik", "5": "Patna"},
        "correct": "3",
        "explanation": "Mandalay is in Myanmar. It was the last royal capital of Burma."},
    "4": {
        "question": "St. George's Channel divides which two countries?",
        "answers": {"1": "UK and Spain", "2": "UK and Ireland", "3": "UK and Belgium", "4": "UK and France", "5": "US and Canada"},
        "correct": "2"},
    "5": {
        "question": "Which of these countries does NOT border Jordan?",
        "answers": {"1": "Syria", "2": "Iraq", "3": "Lebanon", "4": "Saudi Arabia", "5": "Israel"},
        "correct": "3"},
    "6": {
        "question": "Which country extends farthest to the west?",
        "answers": {"1": "Thailand", "2": "Laos", "3": "Malaysia", "4": "Indonesia"},
        "correct": "4"},
    "7": {
        "question": "Which river is NOT among the 10 longest rivers in the world?",
        "answers": {"1": "Yellow River", "2": "Yangtze", "3": "Mekong", "4": "Nile", "5": "Amazon"},
        "correct": "3",
        "answerimage": "Geography-longestrivers.gif",
        "explanation": "The Mekong is #12."},
    "8": {
        "question": "Which country extends farthest to the north?",
        "answers": {"1": "Mali", "2": "Niger", "3": "Chad", "4": "Sudan", "5": "Yemen"},
        "correct": "1"},
    "9": {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Baltic State?",
        "answers": {"1": "Estonia", "2": "Lithuania", "3": "Latvia", "4": "Slovenia"},
        "correct": "4",
        "answerimage": "Geography-balticstates.gif",
        "explanation": "The Baltic States are Estonia, Latvia, and Lithuania, the countries along the east shore of the Baltic Sea."},
    "10": {
        "question": "Which country does NOT border both the Pacific and Atlantic oceans?",
        "answers": {"1": "Colombia", "2": "Brazil", "3": "Chile", "4": "Panama", "5": "Mexico"},
        "correct": "2"}
}
